# Tomás Agustín <u>Caputo</u> Junior <u>FrontEnd</u> developer



### Personal Resume

Technical student in web design and programming.

Focused on finding my first experience as a junior developer / layout designer, where I can provide suitable solutions for the FrontEnd development of static and dinamic websites, learn new development environments and be part of an IT team.

#### Technical Skills

- HTML5 CSS3 (Flex Grids)
- Responsive web Design
- Preprocessor: SASS
- BootStrap 4 5
- JavaScript (Vanilla Ecma)
- GIT GitHub
- Figma Adobe Balsamiq
- WordPress

Practice in the translation of MockUps into code, development of responsive websites for each type of screen, implementation of new features.

#### Contact

- Pilar, Buenos Aires
- Tomas.caputo@hotmail.com
- 04 / 03 / 1996

# Languages / Portfolio

• English, proficiency B.2





### Education / Training courses

Universidad da Vinci, ARG

Web application development | 2021 - 2023

• Currently studying.

### Educación IT, ARG

FrontEnd web development course | 2021 - Present

• Studying complementary course in FrontEnd development.

### CoderHouse, ARG

Web developer | 2021

• Introductory course in web application development.

## Work experience

4 years of experience working in companies in different areas of attention, administration and customer service

• Ski lift operator Vail Resorts, USA | December 2019 - March 2020

- Commercial administrative NRG Motors SRL, ARG | January 2018 - July 2019
- Administrative assistant Bartender Barrás moviles Juan B, ARG | June 2015 - Dec 2017

I will apply communication, teamwork and organization skills learned in my previuos work experiences.

